Hello Namaste Welcome to PolicyAct We give
you expert advice on insurance
without any spam or gix.
To buy a health or term insurance policy, you
can click on the link given in the description box. Today's video is on
ICICI Prudential Life Insurance
plans. This
is an updated plan as of 2025 because ICICI Prudential
Life Insurance plans are quite good.
Why is there so much hype in the market, what is
special about these plans, we will tell you everything
in this video. ICICI
Prudential Life Insurance Company is a
leading private sector insurance company
in India. It offers a wide range of insurance
plans as per the
different needs of the customers. Whether you
want a pure term insurance plan,
an endowment plan, a ULIP plan or a
retirement plan, ICICI
Prudential offers all types of plans.
ICICI Prudential Life
Insurance Company Limited
is a joint venture between ICICI Bank Limited and Prudential
Corporation Holdings Limited.
ICICI Prudential Life Insurance started its
operations in India in 2001.  It was started in 1999
and is now
considered one of the leading insurance companies in the country. The
company's claim settlement ratio (
CSR) is
99.3 and solvency ratio is
191.5. Its life insurance plans offer
hassle-free service, allowing
you to pay your insurance policy premium
online
without requiring any physical visit. They have
trusted customer support and
strong governance and transparency.
ICICI Life Insurance,
registered and regulated by the Insurance Regulatory and Development Authority of India (IRDAI), follows all industry
norms and
maintains standards of ethical practices.
Now, you might be wondering what benefits you will get if you take ICICI Prudential
Life Insurance.
Let us
explain. ICICI Prudential Life
Insurance plans provide financial security to your family. In case of an
untimely or
unfortunate death, these
plans provide peace of mind.
FinanciallyExpress.com
is a popular and reputed insurance
provider and ICICI Prudential Life
Insurance offers its customers
insurance plans at affordable rates.
The company
offers some special benefits for female customers, such as a 15%
lifetime discount on premiums.
Salaried women also get an
extra discount of up to 15% on the first year's premium. The
next advantage is that
customers
can easily manage their policies through the ICICI Life Insurance
login portal. They
can pay their premiums, update their personal
information, and file claims. You
also get five riders
with ICICI Life Insurance:
Waiver of Premium, Critical
Illness Rider, Accidental Death Rider,
Permanent and Partial Disability Rider,
Income Benefit Rider. So, this was the complete review
of ICICI Prudential Life Insurance plans.
If you are wondering about
any specific thing about ICICI,  If you want to know
then please tell us by commenting and do
not forget to like and subscribe the video
and to take any health or term insurance
policy you
can check the link given in the description box till then buy
and take care